[
    {
        "question": "She ____ a doctor.",
        "options": ["are", "is", "have", "am"],
        "correct": 1,
        "sec": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "I ____ hungry.",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are", "be"],
        "correct": 0,
        "sec": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "They ____ from France.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 1,
        "sec": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "He ____ playing tennis.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 0,
        "sec": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "We ____ happy.",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are", "be"],
        "correct": 2,
        "sec": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "You ____ my best friend.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 1,
        "sec": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "She ____ in London.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 0,
        "sec": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "They ____ at home.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 1,
        "sec": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "He ____ a teacher.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 0,
        "sec": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "I ____ from Japan.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 2,
        "sec": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "We ____ good students.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 1,
        "sec": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "She ____ her homework.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 0,
        "sec": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "They ____ watching TV.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 1,
        "sec": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "He ____ at the park.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 0,
        "sec": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "We ____ in the same class.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am", "be"],
        "correct": 1,
        "sec": 15
    }
]
